<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Japlans</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Japlans</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 16:55:03 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>What on Earth Is DisneySea</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/what-on-earth-is-disneysea/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 16:55:03 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/what-on-earth-is-disneysea/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;What on Earth is DisneySea?&#xA;Well, as a massive Disney fan myself, I could argue that any Disney theme is worth the visit. However, what strikes out about DisneySea is that it is the only one of its kind in the world, and importantly, it is in Tokyo! The first place on our Itinerary! How could I not?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Disneysea has a theme of, you guessed it, the sea! It also features characters that haven’t yet been featured in any other park such as Rapunzel, as well as its own character Duffy, a bear character, just as popular as Mickey Mouse in Asia.&#xA;The latest expansion of the park, Fantasy Springs, brings to life a Peter Pan, Tinkerbell, Frozen, and Tangled rides which I’d be lying if I said this wasn’t a major draw for me!&#xA;I was at first concerned that Fantasy Springs would be a timed area and/or a priority line for all the rides, however it was recently announced that as of the 1st April 2025 that there will only be standby lines – the typical queue experience. I for one think this is a great decision because who doesn’t want to experience the wonder of the lantern festival from Tangled?&#xA;The next step was persuading Eddie, who, while I’m certain enjoyed our trip to Disneyland Paris in 2023 was less keen when we had all of Japan to choose between! The compromise for us was one Disney park and Japan has two main theme parks, both in Tokyo on the same site, Disneyland Tokyo and DisneySea. In an ideal world, we would go to both and choose our favourite, however, this is not a Disney trip and we want to pack as much of Japan into our trip as physically possible. Plus I wanted to also go to Universal Studios Japan and there’s only so much money and theme parks Eddie and I can take! From all my research Disneyland Tokyo appears to be similar to Disneyland Paris which was a trip we went on in 2023. Eddie and I decided that it would be a more unique experience to go to DisneySea, so Disneysea it was!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Check out our new Itinerary!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/new-itinerary/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 14:48:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/new-itinerary/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Just a quick update, our itinerary can now be found on our website or on our Instagram account! You can find it, or the link to the instagram page in the top right of the website!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Japan?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/why-japan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2025 12:48:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/why-japan/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As I&amp;rsquo;m sat here in a cosy cottage in Wales nestled in the Wye Valley, admiring the wonder and natural beauty of the landscape around me, I can&amp;rsquo;t help but reflect on the similar wonders that attracted me to Japan in the first place. Now a question I&amp;rsquo;ve been asked more times than I can count, whenever I&amp;rsquo;ve mentioned over the years that I&amp;rsquo;m planning on travelling to Japan in the foreseeable future, &lt;strong&gt;&amp;ldquo;Why Japan?&lt;/strong&gt; A simple question at first glance, and yet every time the question has been asked I&amp;rsquo;ve shrugged it off and mumbled some combination of &amp;ldquo;&lt;em&gt;The landscape&lt;/em&gt;&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;&lt;em&gt;The nerd culture&lt;/em&gt;&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;&lt;em&gt;The crazy technology&lt;/em&gt;&amp;rdquo;, never really being able to concisely answer on the spot. So, with some time, thought and discussion with Hannah I&amp;rsquo;ve tried to pin down the answer and put it on paper.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to our adventure!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 14:48:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/first-post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I remember it clearly, I sat in my desk chair in the bedroom of our university house, no doubt playing some kind of video game rather than completing any coursework. Sun beaming in through the white sheer curtains we&amp;rsquo;d put up for privacy at the beginning of the year. I was in my third year of University studying Geology, while Hannah was completing her Masters degree in Archaeological Science, the year was 2020 and Wales was still in a semi-lockdown. Hannah could leave the area for educational reasons, to attend Cardiff Uni, while I was bound to the local area, if not ideally the house itself. I remember hearing Hannah come home from morning lectures, calling up the stairs to say she was home, then after some time the bedroom door creaked open, Hannah stepped through the threshold with a smile on her face, saying one sentence that would set a course for the next five years of our lives. &lt;strong&gt;&amp;ldquo;Hey Eddie? What would you think of living in Japan?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
